ED
Q. Souvenirs?
Souvenirs?
I, uh, uh, uh, originally I never buy souvenirs.
I decided not to buy them because I would eat a lot of extra food,
But recently I have started buying them.
That's right. That's why I didn't have anyone to give them to,
But recently, I have more friends to give them to.
So I finally started buying them.
I used to buy only for myself,
But now I have more friends.
Please ask your father.
Please, for your father.
All right.
Matt, Mike, please.
Hey!
Where are we?
Okinawa!
We are ABTU!
ABTU!
Go this way. It's open. Let's go.
Let's keep on copying!
Attendance number is Ayaki Happongi.
Please give me your best regards.
♪♪ SmartWay
Yes, so, in no time at all, the next 2days in Okinawa will be the last song.
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
We will see you again.
The aftermath and postmortem of A was a lot of personal matters.
Ah~
Oh, something about it.
Everyone's thoughts are growing on me.
You understand, don't you?
Yes, I do. So, even so, the next one is the last.Yes, I am. So, still, the next is the last.
Wait a minute.
I'm sweating like never before.
Why?
Something happened.
What happened?
I was fine.
Is it bad?
There was a bridge called Meiji-bashi, right?
It's near Donki,
I thought it was called Daichi Bridge,
The earth. I thought of it as the earth inside my stomach,
I thought it was a bridge where such a life was born, and I was grateful.
I thought it was a nice name, and when I approached it, I found it was the Meiji Bridge.
I was thinking that in my head,
Oh, I was talking about how I had done it.
Let's have a strategy meeting.